Eren...
Go, Eren!
Fight!
Huh? Mikasa...
Let's head back.
What am I doing here?
Since That Day
That day, humanity remembered...
It's one of them...
A Titan!
the terror of being ruled by them.
The humiliation of being kept in a cage.
It broke...
a hole in the wall...
They're coming inside!
The Titans are getting inside!
We have to get out of here!
Eren!
My house is over there...
My mom!
Mikasa!
Nothing hit my house!
Once I turn that corner,
my house will still be there!
Welcome home.
You actually worked hard for a change.
I won't let you.
Joining the Survey Corps?
Don't be stupid.
Mom!
Eren...
Mikasa, grab that side!
Hurry, Mikasa!
I know.
Eren, take Mikasa and run!
I want to run!
So hurry and get out of there!
Hannes!
Take the children and run!
Don't underestimate me, Karla.
I'll defeat the Titan, and save you all!
Wait!
Don't try to fight it!
Wait, Hannes!
What are you doing?!
Thank you.
My mom is still back there!
Eren! Mikasa!
You must survive!
Stop!
Hey, what are you doing?
The ship's full!
It's leaving!
You fool...
Where are you aiming?
The gate...
It's closing!
We need to retreat.
We'll be left behind!
Don't close it yet...
Wait a little more!
Many people are still in the city!
Close the gate!
The Titans are coming!
Get that gate shut!
Fire!
It's coming! Run!
It's over...
It's over.
Humanity will be devoured by Titans again.
Eren...
The reason you couldn't save your mother
is that you lacked the strength.
I'll kill them all!
I'll wipe every one of them...
off the face of this earth!
The Year: 850
Today, you trainee graduates will be given
three choices.
You can join the Garrison,
protecting towns and reinforcing the walls.
Or the Survey Corps, who risk their lives
beyond the walls, in Titan territory.
Or the Military Police, who serve the King,
lead the people, and protect internal order.
Now it's our turn
to devour the Titans!
It's been five years since then...
Humanity is finally regaining its dignity.
We can win!
Our counterattack
has only begun!
So hot!
Wh-What is that?
That was close...
The wall has been breached?
Not again...
The Titans will come inside the walls again!
I will annihilate all of you!
Annihilate all of you...
Fixed cannon maintenance team 4,
prepare for combat!
Our target is the Colossal Titan before us!
This is our chance!
Don't let it get away!
Too slow!
You're mine!
Go!
I missed?
No...
The Colossal Titan vanished?
If they make it through,
we'll relive the tragedy that
befell us five years ago!
We stop the Titans here!
But I do have one request.
Please... Don't die.
I'm not going to die.
I can't die here.
Team 34, advance!
Support the vanguard!
An Aberrant!
Stop!
How dare you?!
Eren!
Wait!
I'll avenge Thomas...
I won't let you get away!
Eren!
Why
can't I
move?
Eren!
I can't die here...
Eren! Hurry!
It wasn't supposed to be this way.
Why do they take everything from us?
Our lives.
Our dreams...
Why?
You must master this power!
I won't give up!
I'll eliminate them all...
I'll kill them myself!
I'll wipe them off the face
of the earth.
Every single one!
More...
I want to kill...
A Titan killing another Titan?
Kill...
more...
Eren, don't you know who I am?
It's me, Mikasa!
Your family!
You must use that boulder
to seal the hole!
Move, Ackerman!
What?
What... am I doing now?
Am I sitting?
I can't see a thing.
What day is it?
Where am I?
Hmm?
I'm at home?
I'll go back to sleep.
He will become a Titan,
pick up the giant boulder
by the shattered gate,
carry it over, and seal the hole.
I don't know if I can use the
Titan's power to lift that boulder.
But I understand what I must do...
I must become a symbol
of hope for everyone!
I'll do it...
I'll make this happen!
Armin, that's insane! Stop!
Mikasa, do what you can!
If you go, some lives might be saved!
Leave Eren to me!
Eren, can you hear me?
Come to your senses!
If we don't get out of
here, we'll all die!
Don't let the Titan's body take over!
Just come out of that
lump of flesh, now!
One 13-meter class!
It's approaching Jaeger!
More Titans coming through the hole!
Four Titans, approximately
10-meter class!
Captain, we're finished!
We're the last ones left!
We should recall them
to defend the gate.
Shall I do it?
No.
Shouldn't we order the
elite force to retreat?
No.
Continue drawing the Titans
to the edge of town.
Eren! Get out of there!
Hurry!
Eren! Eren!
What happened to avenging your mother?
Aren't you going to wipe out the Titans?
Don't you hate the things
that killed your mother?
What are you talking about, Armin?
Mom's right here...
Eren! Eren!
Wake up, Eren!
You're still in there, aren't you?
If we stay here, the
Titans will kill us!
Everything will end here!
Like I said...
I don't understand you, Armin.
Why do I have to leave?
Yeah...
Why would I want to leave?
The outside world...
Wouldn't it be great if, one day,
we could go explore the outside world, too?
The outside world!
I am going to exterminate all of the Titans,
and escape these cramped walls!
That is my dream...
Eren... Answer me!
You knew that hell was one
step beyond the walls.
You might die horribly,
like my mom and dad did.
So why did you want to go?
Why?
You know why.
Because I was born into this world!
Eren...
Mikasa!
Armin!
Eren won!
Now he's trying to get the job done!
If we can cover him till
he gets to the gate,
we win!
Defend him at all costs!
Protect Eren until he reaches the gate,
even if it costs you your life!
Don't let any of the Titans near him!
From the time we are born,
we are free...
It doesn't matter how strong
those who would deny
us that freedom are...
Flaming water... Frozen earth...
I don't care what it is!
The one who sees them
will be the freest person in the world!
Fight...
I'd willingly give my life for that!
It doesn't matter how
terrifying the world is.
cruel the world is!
Fight...
Fight!
Go, Eren!
What am I doing here?
You're so out of it.
Were you sound asleep?
No...
It's just, I feel like I had a really long dream.
What was it about?
I can't remember...
Eren, why are you crying?
Answer up, you piece of crap.
What do you want to do?
I want to join the Survey Corps
and just slaughter the Titans!
The time for dreams is over.
Eren wakes in the dim and damp underground jail cell,
only to face a special military tribunal
that will decide his fate.
Still Can't See
Night Before the Counteroffensive (1)